this is EDD clone EC details back with
another episode and today we made a
switch we made a switch to
ammo ammo car care products now if you
don't know what this is about I'm going
to play a clip here cuz you should all
know who Larry is Play a clip principles
103 is the essential detailing tools
this isn't like fun things to have or
cool I'm talking about the meat and
potatoes of detailing so lar castella
guy is a freaking Beast right the way he
details is just magical uh I've been
watching Larry for a super long time
been trying to get him on podcast for a
super long time probably never going to
happen but for watching this Larry I did
email
you first time you responded second time
you ghosted me I don't want to be the
ex-girlfriend nonetheless I'm going to
give you a fair review the question I'm
going to have today is or the question
I'm trying to answer for everyone is is
this worth your money is M9 worth your
change right they don't do gallons now
some of the products are deletable the
other ones you have to use straight out
of the bottle I want to go over the
whole line with you we are going to use
90% of these chemicals today okay I got
to clean this whole truck before I take
my wife to go see my dad um and this
truck has to get detailed the sun is out
outside but it's cold but I've only
washed one side of the truck and all my
videos and the other side has been
neglected we have like muddy uh we're
going to use Titan to see how it works
on rubber and then we're going to dress
them so let me go over the product line
with you and we'll discuss what each one
does so right now I have foam paint
cleanser uh this one is just a foam
shampoo uh let's go over the smell let's
see what the smell's about
huh let's see m
smells interesting smells good smells
real good um the cool thing about Ammo
stuff is he says to squeeze so there's
no like put 4 oz inside of a foam can it
says give it three squeezes put it in so
we have their foam shampoo we have their
boost anti salt so this is a additive I
call it an additive it gets put inside
with your soap or your brute wheel fo
and in a wheel bucket it gives it some
more cleaning properties anti-corrosive
anti salt so we're going to pair these
up today um for the body and the paint
and then we have our frothy now if you
don't know about frothy I'll put a a
video I've done here frothy is are
hoseless wash this stuff this stuff is
absolutely busting like frothy is very
dilutable it smells pretty good um and
it's
expensive yeah it's pretty expensive I
think it's like 30 bucks for that we
have their drying Aid which is hydrate
this is their new formula so it's a
little thinner I had the old one where
it was a thick like lotion it was like
Coco butter for the car this one I'm
going to use as a drying Aid today on
this vehicle and that's going to be our
outside wash procedure we're going to go
to this side of the I had to break this
up dude there are so many bro there are
so many chemicals I had to break this up
okay walk you through this um we're
going to use dir brute this one believe
it or not it's a low acidic one so this
is a peach of four wheel soap
specifically designed to give you the
strength needed to clean rims made for
those days when you escape for an hour
like and he goes through a whole Spiel
of beautiful symmetry tree and like pet
Tree in back of the bottle and then when
you get to after you read your love
letter from uh Larry you go to the
bottom says Direction always use
protective gloves cuz this is low acidic
add three squeezes of brute to a
designated wheel bucket fill up half
with uh hose water and then it says
rinse down the wheel and then remove the
L uh uh remove the loose dirt and grime
and then with that we're going to use
our Plum wheel cleaner here so these two
are paired together will bucket uh I was
going to actually try to foam that on to
see if I can get get the foam we'll see
we'll see what happens this one says
it's a strong yet safe cleaner that
sticks to the wheels and releases and
braided baked uh brake dust best used on
excessive dirty rims pre-rinse wheel
with water spray liberally on the rims
clean it so this will be our pre-spray
and then I'm going to use the wheel of
the The Brute and foam bucket and then
we have mud tire dressing I heard this
stuff was busting so we're going to do
that for the tire dressing itself and
this one's a unique one for me this
one's
$20 $20 like what's that this is a
degreaser this is the Titan 12 Degreaser
High Peach soap safe Degreaser used on
paint engines interior oilbased stains
commonly used on door jams wheel whs
parts of the vehicle where heavy Road
oils live so I'm going to use this
actually for the wheel wells and then
we're going to use this for the rubber
mats inside the car I mean we talked
about their exterior package right I
went over all that stuff uh I'll put the
price in the description below I believe
each one of these are no less than 19
bucks each with the high being 35 for
froy uh we have this one this this is
their lather I believe this was 19 bucks
this is their interior cleanser you
spray it on it gives you that dope foam
I call it that dope foam I also want
crazy right and brought shag cuz I
wanted to test shag carpet cleaner and
this is their siphon uh coffee uh
cleanser so this one itself is um it's a
low PH so this is acidic right this
would be acidic to remove the coffee
stains and things that nature this is a
little more uh pH high pH so these two
should balance off I didn't buy the
other one cuz I didn't have a for it but
uh I did buy that one and then we have
our glass oey I'm on the market for a
good glass CLE so if this is great I'll
buy like four bottles and us it my
bottles and then I bought
his he's going all out here and then we
have last but not least this is their
moose interior dressing so that's all
the products I have I'm going to show
you how we're going to dilute it we're
going to foam on the car talk about the
cleaning power we're going to do the
rims and let's get going first thing
we're going to do is get our stuff ready
right I like to prep my stations before
I touch anything so let me fill up the
buckets I filled those up let me show
you what I'm going to do the foam cans
we're going to use two mtms the goats
we're going to put one with foam plus uh
boost the other one's going to be brutes
I'm going to do the three squeezes like
you said of the foam and two squeezes of
the brute and that and I'm going to put
them in in a whe bucket and then what
we're going to do is prep the cars so
I'm going to do the inside first the
inside's Pretty Dirty for our standards
right let me show you this so we're
going to go around take all the mats out
the mats need to be clean we're going to
use Titan for that we're going to blow
we're going to take all the uh bigger
items out of the car then we're going to
blow it out and then vacuum I do a light
vacuum first and then at the end of it I
do a heavy vacuum so I can gauge how the
Fabrics look there's one part of the
seat on the driver's side that looks
like I get to use Shack so I'm pretty
stoked about that and then what I start
to do is I start to clean the panels
we're going to take on uh interior
cleaner uh make sure you put gloves on I
don't know what the pH is is I didn't
look it up we're going to use our
utility towels from autofiber and then
we're going to do section by section I
always go inside out to learn that from
Ian but for this sake of this demo I'm
just going to show you this door we'll
do all the dirty bits we'll use Titans
for the pedals cuz they're going to need
it and then we're going to clean all the
inside first then we'll tackle the
dressing and then mousse doesn't look
dirty but there's a lot of Grease here
and I've been testing other products
that are kind of weird the the first
thing I noticed about these is this
sucks okay $20 for this sprayer sucks
big you know what so I'm going to take
it smells freaking good not going to I'm
going to spray it on and look at that uh
I don't know if this is an APC but the
foam on that is
wild you can see that I tried to just
test it you don't want to I don't like
to use a lot I like to spray in uh my
brush and then I'll go Section by
section but it gives you good foam uh it
looks like it cleans you know the
ability to clean and foam are not
correlated meaning that you don't need
foaming to clean that's just the
industry selling you stuff that they
want to sell you cuz they think I think
is going to do a good job cleaning if
you can see it foam easy to wipe off you
can tell there's dirt on the panel like
I I mentioned there's a lot of
Grease man smells
great uh workability you see that so it
is uh pulling off of dirt just for that
section there is some grease on this
side we're going to pull you in a little
closer and take you
downtown uh right
here and
then
so like I said I I just like to go
Section by
section play some music if I was by
myself I'll be jamming to some Spanish
music I can see why you would buy this
though not going to drw uh it's a
pleasure to use actually we'll see how
it tackles real dirt outside of the
panels it does uh it does let you set up
so I let this dry a tiny bit here and it
does let you set up here so if you see
this right
if I hit it it lets me foam it up so it
stays on there for a while so you can
foam it take my
microfiber yeah dude this is this is a
nice Cent cleaner I really it took
everything back to
neutral this is It's Pleasant all right
so we're going to test it here you can
tell it's dirty I'm going to spray
lather on there you can use a thing but
I want you to see up close the kind of
foam you get
yeah from this
product and like I said the smell is
awesome I always hit it all and you can
tell some of the dirt that's coming off
here and then we're going to take that
and look how it flashes off yeah that's
a good product man lather is impressive
we have this here we're going to tackle
that part
of man I would buy this if Larry you
made a gallon dude just just the sheer
enjoyment of it lathering on and getting
that idea of your cleaning is freaking
awesome take
that and then look at the Plastics
here make sure that I'm not too
high the seat so I did this section
already and you can see the panels here
they look very good that side so we have
this dirt on the seat here um I'm going
to just what he does in the video is
just sprays on some lather get a little
a little brush I'm using a lithium brush
and I'm telling you that this smell is
an amazing interior smell uh that was
enough to do the whole
seat and you can see from a bird's eye
view that I did the whole seat you want
to get inside of the crevices and it
flashes off real
good and then we're going to grab our
microfiber here and where's it at where
where the freak are you where you at put
it away this stuff this this uh five
stars five out of five I love the
cleaning I love the smell you know what
it reminded me of it reminded me of pns
Express mixed with Hyper cleanse but it
kept the seat soft I don't know how to
explain it this stuff is great this
stuff is absolutely um it's amazing I
wish they made a gallon if he made a
gallon that would be a game-changing uh
formula no joke um right now what we're
going to do is uh
we're going to do an interior dress so I
I did clean all of the
Interior um let me talk about the
interior for a second the interior was
dirty right it wasn't the dirtiest
interior in the world but look if you're
looking for like a a disaster detail
you're going to have to go to like mad
detailings or watch ammo um but this is
our car I'm trying to get it ready
before I leave so we come back we got
clean cars and the inside is absolutely
H for us hammered so I am going to dress
the seats uh what we have here is moose
interior conditioner I never used it
before I've never used lather this one
States be sure the leather is cleansed
uh to cleanse use lather uh massage
mousse into the areas be thorough and
apply mousse uh with complete coverage
so this would motorize to hide fill in
with good stuff for leather cleanse so
this is a mousse this is uh interior
conditioner it says leather but um the
back says leather but it's interior
conditioner I want to show you the
consistency consistency so if you look
at that there
right there it is
creamy um and it smells just like
leather uh smell is what I'm getting so
tighten up the top uh we're going to
pour some here so you can see it so you
get that creamy looks like you shouldn't
eat it type of vibe and then we're going
to do the seat together and I'll show
you what that looks like that in you can
see how it moisturizes it it gives me
lithium hide
Vibes and you want to be careful cuz
when you have these seats with the
little holes in it you can get some of
that weird uh lotion inside of those
seats so I'm going to see if I could do
this side but look how it looks it's not
offputting you can tell that it wants to
seep in the seats it does work on Tesla
seats fake leather seats and it gives
you a nice Vibe I always flip it around
and I come in and there it goes nice
looking nice looking is a great interior
um conditioner for seats I tried a piece
on the plastic wasn't my favorite to
apply but on the seats I would put it up
there with any of the Interior dressings
I got I think I might just do a versus
Kosh KMI I think Kosh KMI leather star
or km I don't know call it what you will
dog uh leather star hits a little
different for me in my opinion but this
is good I like the consistency of it
gives me that old school Vibe uh the
smell is intoxicating and the seats look
wonderful so we're going to tackle shag
uh and shag we spot right
here that we're um trying to get out so
I'm going to spray shag on it I'm going
let that sit for a second I'm going
massage it in and you can just see how
shag starts to have some foaming agents
and then I'll start to brush the smell
it's a nice cleaning smell kind of
like I don't know smells wonderful
though reminds me a nice cleaning smell
I brush that I'm going to take my spot
here and look good as new baby uh I
don't how shag is going to work I don't
know how ammo shag is going to work on
the beat up cars but so far for little
little stains like this or salt stains
that took it out on the car we're going
to use Titan the Greaser that sip for a
little bit while it breaks down the dirt
here but you can see it here man don't
don't don't Bree that
in get that brush in
there all right cool cleaned it all
up
this stuff is good as a Degreaser we'll
try it on the mats cuz they're a little
dirty just don't breathe it in cuz
you'll choke to death we're going to
spray that on and I'm going to let that
sit for a little bit you can see how it
breaks down the dirt when I spray that
on I'm going to take my brush
here dip it in my wheel
thing yep let that
sit and then we're going to spray that
off the smell though like you can tell
it's just a a hard chemical like it hits
your thr
good here we go it's got to clean I got
to clean that white part of the tundra
but so far so good wheels on this
side is not that bad The Wheels on the
other side are bad that's the
fender so I'm going to see if this
brute could be sprayed on the whole
thing to clean it and then I'm going to
take Plum and what Plum
does here it's a wheel cleaner so Plum
turns purple so I think it does that for
show
we'll get that all over the wheel let
that sit and then I'm going to foam on
brute Plum on Plum on Plum wheel Plum
wheel is kind of unique cuz it comes out
purple so you don't know if it's doing
anything I don't think it has any type
of iron removers in it but it's supposed
to break down iron particles we're going
to foam on brute on the whole wheel and
Fender we're going to start cleaning
I'll give you my thoughts this is
brute that's literally one squeeze
inside of the oh that soap is crazy you
see Plum you see Plum reacting I'm going
to take my spoke cleaner here put it
inside of my
bucket and you can see the grime coming
off of the wheel like it's breaking up
the dirt like it
should go in my bucket
again
okay I'm going to
take my face brush
here I have to get this on
here and see if that would start
breaking up some of that that Grime on
the tire there is a sealant on
there
all right all right okay make me a
Believer no so listen the tire system
for me I need to test against what I
currently use right now I'm using total
whe Tire cleaner or ads 4 to1 I'm still
testing both and I just used an ik
sprayer spray it on I'm using one
chemical this one uh in the iron remover
when I needed this one required me to
use soap in a bucket Plum had to foam it
on to get that consistency but it was it
worked good like the tires look good
I'll show you what the tires look like
right now so they look good and uh it
did a good job cleaning the dirt like it
was Heavy dirt on some of the rims that
haven't cleaned because of YouTube so
right now what we're going to do is foam
the car let's talk about the foaming
process that they suggest so we have
Boost which is their salt anti salt
situation and then we have their foam um
and the directions for this is this
squeeze two two or three squeezes in the
foam cannon that's my kind of directions
kids let's look at how the foam Works
we're going to let it sit around the car
we're going to do a contact watch I
never pre-spray the car first cuz I want
to see how the foam does
interact
so that's the
foam and you can see it's it's a nice
clingy foam on actually smells good the
MTM is that it doesn't go through a lot
of products so you can see here where
the product is still pretty
Co and you can tell here that this side
is super dirty I haven't watched this
side at all I've only done YouTube
videos on one
side
as a foam Cannon soap this is pretty
good as a soap uh foam Cannon soap it
does a good
job works on ammo so it goes on thick
and then begins this part of like
breaking down you can see it pulling
down dirt on the floor and it's not the
thickest snow foam but it cleans that's
a good soap that is a good soap yeah
good soap so a couple things I noticed
about this foam soap it goes on clingy
it stays on for a while had it sitting
on the car for about 2 3 minutes I'm
going to start my contact wash and then
we'll go over a few things so
slick yeah it's super slick to the paint
is it slicker than any other soap uh I
get ads
Vibes how slick that is super slick and
you can tell that it's cleaning there's
some cleaning properties happening with
the Boost boost being a
acidic so anything acidic on the coating
always brings it back you
know man it is slick slick to the touch
soap was soap is great but here's the
thing I had to add two soaps in one to
make it real good not sure boost gives
it slickness but it gives it it's super
slick man like real slick it has great
cleaning properties it breaks dirt down
it sits on the paint but then it breaks
down to pull down I'm going to show you
the car right now and you can see this
is just after contact wash what we have
left let's look at spray
off yeah it's it's good Larry uh Take a
Bow you probably don't even care what
I'm thing but you sir that soap is great
no cap I washed the car turned out great
okay I'm excited about this we're going
to go hydrate as my drying Aid um it put
says put a spray per panel I'm going to
show you the panel here we're going to
use my mother mother floer and we'll go
here and try it dude I don't know I feel
like it's 2018 again and I just bought
this we're going to spray here spray
here and I always spray one on a pan
white
wet and I'm going to see if I could do
it my normal
way so look at it I pre-sprayed the
whole panel here and then I'mma come
down and dry and that is smell is
phenomenal it's like
berries yeah no streaks on the glass
high humidity in here it's about 80°
after
washing and look at this side look how
glossy that
is
yeah I've always enjoyed hydrate even
the thick stuff hydrate is great I'm
going to finish dying the car here's
where we're at we washed the car we
cleaned the inside we did all that crap
the last thing I always do on to detail
is clean the inside glass we're going to
use the ammo uh squeegee never used a
squeegee before in my life we're going
to use obey ammo obey we're going to use
my streak freak or whatever this is from
this is probably the best drying the
best cleaning towel I've used compar
compared to drive me River I like this
one better from
autofiber and then let's go to work I'll
show you this glass here like I said I
don't do I don't do this a lot so oey
says
to spray it on and it sticks right you
see how that sticks on the glass now
what he does is he comes in he does that
he does that he does that and then he
comes in and he cleans
it
that's a nice glass cleaner so that's
how I would use it U I'm going to do the
rest of the car we'll uh end the video
in a second scale ammo in terms of as a
Company products I used every single
product in line I even have the ceramic
coating I'm going to put on this weekend
how would I rank their chemicals right
Skilling 1 to 108 and 1 half the reason
I gave it one and a half it would have
been a 10 cuz here's why he doesn't sell
gallons for a professional this is cost
for you if you are a consumer or someone
who loves to detail their cars this is
worth buying okay I'm going to tell you
which ones you want to go get now and
the why okay let me tell you this um
shag fabric I need more time with I have
dctal and gico that I think might be a
taded better uh brute wheel uh I need to
test that more for me Brute wheel didn't
fill a gap in my space I have total
Wheel and Tire cleaner 46 bucks like by
gallon uh this one was I think was $16
or $18 for this one and you use you go
through a bit of it if you're watching
your wheels for me it was hit and miss
it is a low PH uh it's acidic so it's a
four right I could probably use perif on
my wheels probably get same results
perif starts at one that L bow and I get
a gallon uh the Moose interior for the
seats at first I was like this is trash
but Lord bro I'm going be honest with
you I have vegan seats in this Toyota I
enjoyed this the I enjoyed the scent I
enjoyed the application I need to test
it against hide but if you're in the
market of trying something as a consumer
even a business the Moose the the moose
was real good uh the Shad carpet like I
said we need some more time I didn't try
hyphen this Degreaser I I I'm on the
fence about we have Grime wave if you
don't know what Grime wave is lithium
Degreaser cleanser I I would say it's
better than this for 20 bucks uh hard
pass on that but it it did clean well
right just for $2 you're only getting 16
oz frothy you need to try frothy is
amazing these two right here are meant
for each other and I know why now he did
it so I love the freaking foam the soap
was a chef's kiss here's what here's
what I learned these two were made for
each
other you know kissing on the tree kis
say came out you know foam toown USA
whatever you want to say these two
Belong Together these two are tremendous
together it sticks on the paint it
cleans it it revives the coating it's
easy to clean it's slick and it spray
off is phenom phal these two I wish I
wish dude I would I would buy these
again these two for sure again and that
is foam paint cleanser and boost antio
those two together were a chef kiss I
didn't try them separately I wasn't you
know like I was just following his video
so lather
lather Larry come here Larry grab grab a
seat Larry I know you're too rich to
hear this okay you're on a different
you're different Echelon different pace
scale but hear me out bro how you going
to have this right that's so freaking
good and then only sell it in this 16 o
why are you doing that to me why are you
doing that to me why are you doing that
to Carlos R why why are you doing that
to Jamie look look Larry this this if
you're on the market to buy one thing
you say Eddie what should I buy that one
thing to try lather it was a pleasure to
use the foam in action to wipe off the
cleaning power I use it on Plastics
Leathers I even use it on parts of the
carpet it was freaking good the smell
phenomenal the smell was phenomenal uh
Plum wheel cleaner did a good job
cleaning I need more time with that but
you you should try this I love the way
it looks I like the way it cleans the
tires I like the way it was breaking
down the mud it did a great job that
paired with brute wheel I think those
two need to go together to to be a full
kit um the mud tire dressing
dude yes I let it dry it's got a good
look this is probably up there with some
of some of the best tire dressings that
I've have used what not to get what not
to get yet um here's what you don't
get come
here if you don't have money don't
get it's hard to pick something bad on
his line everything to me was okay from
okay to Great uh the Degreaser I
wouldn't spend my money on um the
foam man it's tough the glass okay okay
the one thing I wouldn't get is a glass
cleaner wasn't a fan of the way he does
it I think there are other better glass
cleaners that you could buy and Bo that
make more sense I think of Stoners right
goated I think of uh coach kmy that I've
been trying is super good view from pns
niito those things that glass cleaner
for me the expense plus the cost of the
squeegee was not my favorite that's
that's a hit uh shag like I said I don't
know the capabilities of this I need to
test it but I don't believe it could
stand I don't believe it could stand
toe-to-toe with gleo and dual with that
said I want to say this if you're on the
market to try a Cool brand that's been
around he's been in a business he makes
dope content that are worth something
even though sprayers suck and Larry your
sprayers freaking suck okay look how you
going have something like this and then
this trash I I I don't get sprayer is po
trash but the instructions make sense
you know squeeze two or three in you
don't have to worry about measuring
squeeze uh it's a Cool vibe dude on the
market to buy something to
try that you think it's all hype I would
try ammo it lives up to the hype to me
it lived up to the hype
um I really enjoyed the process of
cleaning like I said the the Greaser is
good it's just not for 20 bucks I would
not buy this I'm no that's that's one
flaw for $20 hard fast I'll get grind
wave over that any day of the week F
bomb not yeah there's other stuff but
like the Soaps the the interior lather
the Moose all that stuff bro it's it was
it's great it's great so if you're
watching this hit the Subscribe this
video did cost me
$267 to buy all this no joke I paid out
on my own poet just to test it just to
give you my full review of is it worth
it and I'm telling you if you're a
weekend warrior you're looking for
something to to clean that is an easy
system that does good cleaning and
brings value Amo products are it Amal
products do the trick um are there
cheaper brands that you could you should
try first probably but if you want the
upper echelon products and you want it
to stand on its own two feet I think
ammo does that well I've hit the like we
do have a sponsor Tim from ethos is
sponsoring our 5,000 giveaway he is
giving away a krena he's giving away all
his his chemicals we're going to have
two winners it's going to be a dope dope
giveaway and all you have to do to enter
is hit the Subscribe with that I'm out
thank you for watching peace